tous.com 2015-05-31

# Privacy Policy_us-en

We want you to know how we handle the information you send us via the internet. Our Privacy Policy adapts to the Internet's dynamic environment. We keep you informed by updating this Privacy Policy as our procedures change. Please review it occasionally to remain informed. This Policy was created in February 2011. Our Privacy Policy is explained in more detail below.

#### SHOP WITH CONFIDENCE

TOUS® is committed to protecting our customers' personal information. We use the industry standard encryption protocol known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to keep your order information secure. All orders are transmitted in an encrypted format. To be sure that your order is secure, simply check your Web browser while you are in the ordering section. Most browsers use some sort of symbol to alert you to the fact that you are on a secured website. We will store your shipping and billing information when you create an account with us, but this information will not be used by anyone but TOUS® and the third parties who provide services related to www.tous.com.

At checkout, we require the credit card customer identification number (CVV) with every online purchase made with Credit Cards. The CVV is a 3 or 4 digit, numeric value that provides a cryptographic check of the information embossed on the card. This security feature is designed to protect you against consumer fraud. Your CVV will not be stored on any of our systems and you will need to provide the number every time a purchase is made on www.tous.com. Click here to learn more about CVV.

#### INFORMATION COLLECTED

For those individuals who visit our site but do not make a purchase, we collect and store IP ("Internet Protocol") addresses during the visit. No individualized information is collected, and the IP address is not traced to a particular individual. Similarly, we collect information, using that IP address, about the navigational or browsing activities of our visitors. Again, that information is not tied to any name or other personally identifying information but is used solely to provide demographic data, such as what geographic areas our visitors are from and visitor browsing patterns. For those who make a purchase on www.tous.com, in order to fulfill the order, we collect and store your name, address, shipping information, e-mail address, telephone number, purchase data, and billing information.

#### USE OF THE INFORMATION COLLECTED

We and the third parties who provide services related to www.tous.com will use the information referenced above to fulfill your order and provide services related to www.tous.com or the operation of our business. Examples of these services include payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, order fulfillment and shipping, Web site evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. The third parties who provide any of these services are authorized to use this information only in connection with the services they are engaged to perform.

In addition to using the information referenced above to fulfill your purchase order, we also retain some of that information in our customer database. We use that information to track your order, to respond to your inquiries and to make subsequent purchases you wish to make easier and faster. We also may use that information, from time to time, to contact you concerning our products, services, sales or special promotions of www.tous.com or our corporate affiliates. We try to limit those contacts to ones that might be of interest to you. If you would prefer not to be contacted about our special offers, products or services, please notify us at the following e-mail address: tous@tous.com.

We currently send e-mails only to those www.tous.com customers who are interested in receiving information about our products and services. If you have previously received such e-mails, but no longer want to, contact us by the email referenced above. Please be advised that since promotions may already be in process at the time of your request, it may take several days before electronic contacts cease.

#### STORAGE OF THE INFORMATION COLLECTED

Currently, the www.tous.com customer information that we maintain is stored in our internet database. We limit access to that information to those within our organization with a business need to know. Most of our employees do not have access to that information. In addition, we enforce a policy against unauthorized disclosure or use of the information you share with us, and we instruct our employees concerning that policy. Those employees that do have access are required to abide by our privacy policy. We also require that those third parties who provide services to us and may have access to customer information (such as the third parties who provide Web site, customer service, data collection, storage and reporting services and mail vendors) share our commitment to maintaining your privacy and adhere to our company´s nondisclosure requirements. As stated above, we do not under any circumstances sell customer information to any outside company or organization nor do we permit any such organization to use customer information for its own business purposes.

In fact, we will release specific information about you only if we are compelled to do so to comply with valid legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order, or a valid administrative request from a law enforcement agency, or in the unlikely situation where we, in good faith, believe such information is necessary to prevent harm to you or others. As with any business, it is possible that as our business develops, we might sell or buy online businesses or other assets. In such transactions, information about customers often is among the transferred assets. Accordingly, in the unlikely event that www.tous.com, or substantially all of its assets related to this Web site, is acquired by a third party, such information may be one of the transferred assets. Under these circumstances www.tous.com would to the extent possible require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this privacy policy. We use secure server technology to keep your personal information - including your billing and account information - as secure as possible. Once your information is stored on our database, we have database security technologies and procedures in place to protect it from access by unauthorized employees or third parties.

#### "COOKIES"

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer´s hard drive. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent such acceptance, which will result in your inability to purchase online from us. We do not retain any individualized information as a result of our use of cookies.

#### SHOP AT WWW.TOUS.COM AND PRIVACY OF CHILDREN

Our site is not directed or marketed to children under the age of 18. We do not intentionally collect or store information on children. If we learn that a child has made a purchase from www.tous.com without his or her parent’s consent, we immediately, upon parental request, void the sale and refund any monies collected on the return of the merchandise.

#### TRADEMARKS & COPYRIGHTS

All materials, including video clips, illustrations, photographs, product, images, artwork, designs, logos and trademarks (collectively, "Content") appearing on this website are the property of S. Tous, S.L. and/or its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, "TOUS®") and are protected by U.S. and international trademark, trade dress and copyright laws. The compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement and assembly) of all content on this site is the exclusive property of TOUS® and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. Permission is granted to electronically copy and print hard copy portions of the website for the sole purpose of placing an order on the site or using the site as a shopping resource. Any other use, including the reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display or performance, of the Content of the website is strictly prohibited.

The name and mark TOUS®, the Bear Design, the Kaos Design, and all other TOUS® related trademarks depicted on this website, whether registered or unregistered, are trademarks or service marks of TOUS®. No other company or individual may use these marks without the express written permission of TOUS®. TOUS® merchandise is available exclusively at TOUS®´ website www.tous-shop.com and at TOUS® retail stores. Customers should be wary of purported TOUS® merchandise sold through unauthorized channels since they may be counterfeit.

#### COUNTERFEIT WARNING

TOUS® merchandise is available exclusively from www.tous.com and TOUS® retail stores. Buyers should be wary of purported TOUS® merchandise sold through unauthorized channels. Beware of counterfeits. An Authenticity Certificate will be issued when you buy any TOUS® piece. It certifies the legitimacy of the product and it is valid regarding any imperfection in production.

Since its foundation in 1920, TOUS® strives to guarantee high quality standards in all its products. All TOUS® jewellery products follow noble metals hallmark: 18 kt Gold (750/000) and Sterling Silver (925/000).

#### PHOTOGRAPHY

Some items may appear slightly larger or smaller than actual size due to screen defaults and photography techniques. Other items may be represented at a larger than actual size in order to clearly show details, or smaller than actual size in order to show the entire item.

#### SALES TAX

Local taxes, if applicable, will be added to your order.
